<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="configuration.xsl"?>

<!-- orcm configuration file. -->

<configuration>

<orcm-log>
  <value>/var/log/orcm/orcm.log</value>
</orcm-log>

<orcm-daemons>
  <nodes>
      <value>bend001</value>
      <value>bend003</value>
      <description>List of all nodes that will have an orcmd. Can be</description>
      <description>expressed as a regular expression.</description>
      <description>If an orcmd doesn't find its local node in this list, it will abort with an error message.</description>
  </nodes>
  <port>
    <value>55805</value>
    <description>Port used by orcmd monitoring daemons - only one daemon
    allowed on a node. Each orcmd will be listening on this port</description>
  </port>
  <cores>
    <value>0,1</value>
    <description>Comma-delimited list of ranges of cores that ORCM
    daemons are to be restricted to using</description>
  </cores>
  <mca-params>
    <description>List of MCA params to be used by
    daemons</description>
    <value>
      sensor_base_sample_rate=5,sensor_heartbeat_rate=10
    </value>
  </mca-params>
</orcm-daemons>

<orcm-aggregators>
  <description>List the nodes that will house an aggregator. Aggregators are
  defined as those daemons that actually record monitoring data into
  the database. Only one aggregator is allowed per node! Aggregators
  do not sample their local data by default. The ID of
  each aggregator is taken from its position in the list, starting at
  zero. The node name "localhost" is reserved to indicate that
  the aggregator will be operating standalone for test purposes - when
  running standalone, the aggregator will default to sampling</description>
  <nodes>
    <value>bend000</value>
    <value>bend014</value>
    <value>bend005</value>
  </nodes>
  <port>
    <value>55810</value>
    <description>Port used by orcmd monitoring daemons - only one daemon
    allowed on a node. Each orcmd will be listening on this port</description>
  </port>
  <cores>
    <value>0,1</value>
    <description>Comma-delimited list of ranges of cores that ORCM
    aggregators are to be restricted to using</description>
  </cores>
  <mca-params>
    <description>List of MCA params to be used by aggregators</description>
  </mca-params>
</orcm-aggregators>

<orcm-schedulers>
  <description>Identify the node(s) that houses the ORCM scheduler(s). Only
  one allowed at this time</description>
  <nodes>
    <value>bend001</value>
  </nodes>
  <port>
    <value>55820</value>
    <description>Port used by orcm scheduler</description>
  </port>
  <mca-params>
    <description>List of MCA params to be used by scheduler</description>
  </mca-params>
  <queues>
    <description>Definition of the queues to be used by the
    schedulers. Each entry is in the form of
    queuename:priority:list-of-nodes, where the list-of-nodes is a
    comma-separated list of node ranges in regular expression. The
    "default" queue is automatically created and will contain all
    nodes not explicitly contained in any other defined queue. The
    default queue has a zero priority
    </description>
  </queues>
</orcm-schedulers>

</configuration>
